Hello, everyone, I'm Tayoni.
Today is Thursday, November 10, 2022,
and I am going to record the 23rd podcast.
How have you all been?
After I uploaded the last video, I went to see my sister's family in the US.
In fact, it's already been a week since I came back from America.
In the meantime, I've been to the US, but at the same time,
I've also been thinking a lot about my future career after finishing my master's programme recently.
And so much time has passed!
Before recording a new podcast today, I took another look at the comments on recent videos.
First of all, in the previous podcast, the 22nd podcast,
I introduced the subscribers' experiences of studying Korean.
However, some people could not see the community posts posted before.
So, with the comments added to the video,
I'm going to make a video with a similar theme to that one again next time.
So, if you wanted to leave a comment, but couldn't, please leave a comment on the previous podcast video.
I will make a video like that again.
And for the first time, I took a video of myself talking in front of the camera,
which was a video of making an apple crumble.
To be honest, I felt unsure when uploading it, but I'm really glad that you guys left a lot of good comments.
There are so many oats left now that I bought as an ingredient back then.
So, in the next vlog, I will try to cook something that I can use leftover oats.
And again, there's something new I've tried in the meantime.
I've made my voice be heard in places other than YouTube.
If you search for my channel name ‘Tayoni’ on Spotify, Amazon Music, and Apple Podcasts now,
you can probably listen to the sixth episode now.
Actually, in the early days of when I started YouTube,
many people made this request in the comments.
But I didn't know how to do it back then, so I just put it off.
So I spend a day searching for it on the Internet.
Then, I uploaded the podcasts to other platforms.
After uploading like that, the locations where you are listening to my podcasts are displayed on the world map,
which is really interesting to see that my voice is heard from all over the world.
Anyway, as I mentioned, I went to the US for a week,
and today I'd like to talk about this short trip.
If you're following my Instagram, you've probably already seen this.
I went to my sister's house in Texas, USA for a week at the end of October.
In fact, she's been living in Texas for quite some time now, but this was the first time I'd actually been to her house.
We had met in the US before, but we had travelled to other cities.
But this time, I went straight to Texas because I was going to see a nephew and a niece I had never met in person.
My sister gave birth to her first child just when the covid just started,
and not long ago she gave birth to her second.
Actually, I really wanted to go see her first child before.
But there were a lot of travel restrictions because of the covid,
and I was busy with various things during my master's degree, so I couldn't easily go there.
So, after submitting my master's dissertation on September 1st,
the thing I wanted to do most was to go to Texas and see my sister.
So, as soon as I finished it, I immediately booked a plane ticket.
And, after packing presents for my sister, brother-in-law, niece and nephew,
I finally boarded the plane to Texas on October 24th.
I will never forget how I felt when I saw my niece and nephew for the first time.
The children I only saw on my phone screen were at my sister's house!
And they were a little smaller, cuter and prettier than in the video or photo.
To be honest, when we first met, I was a little worried that they might feel unfamiliar with me,
but we became close to each other really quickly than I thought.
So while I was in the US, I read a lot of books, did a lot of crafts together,
played as much as possible and tried to spend time.
I went to pick her up at the kindergarten she attends,
went to the kindergarten Halloween party, and went on a picnic in the park.
It was so cute to see her running to me while calling me “이모”,
which made me feel really sad to see time passing every day.
The second child is a newborn baby who had just turned 100 days, so we couldn't play together,
but I fed him, soothed him when crying, and put him to sleep.
It was my first time doing anything like that, which was amazing.
And I felt that it was awesome that my sister has been doing all this with little help from our family.
Actually, I saw her after three and a half years.
So she went through these big events, her pregnancy and childbirth twice, in a period we hadn't seen.
It was a pity that I couldn't be with her during the process due to the covid situation,
but it should get a little easier in the future,
so I think it would be really good if we could meet more often as her children grow up.
Now, I think we should make a promise for next time.
After my short trip to the US, I returned to the UK.
For the first few days after coming back, I think it was a little difficult because I couldn't get used to the jet lag.
Even British daylight saving has just ended, so the time of sunset is getting earlier,
and the temperature has dropped slightly.
So the mood has turned a bit gloomier(?).
So, to lift up the mood again, I made a Christmas wreath,
and I am trying to take as many walks as possible every day.
And at the same time, I am thinking a lot about my future.
Nothing has been decided yet,
but I'm going to spend this period well so that I don't leave any regrets.
How are you all doing?
There must be many people like me who live in places where the weather is getting colder.
I hope you don't shrink in the cold weather and have a lively day.
So, everyone, thank you very much for listening to my podcast today,
and I will come back with another video.
Thank you, everyone. Good-bye!